thrunite-store.com 2015-08-18

# Privacy Policy

**Privacy Statement**

We are fully committed to protecting your privacy. Authorized employees within the company access information collected from individual customers on a need-to-know basis only. We do not sell, market or otherwise share any of our customers’ information with any third parties, and will not do so, unless required for the purposes of litigation and only to the appropriate authorities. We constantly review our systems and data to ensure the best possible service to our customers. We will investigate any such actions with a view to prosecuting and/or taking civil proceedings to recover damages against those responsible.

**Confidentiality**

We will not sell, share, or rent your personal information to any third party or use your e-mail address for unsolicited e-mail. Any e-mails sent by this Company will only be in connection with the provision of agreed services and products. You have the right to notify us at any time to cancel your e-mail subscription to our Customer newsletter, as well as any further communications not directly related to the fulfillment of said Customer’s order, or in response to communications initiated by the Customer.

**Security**

We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

**How we use cookies**

A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer's hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyse web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.

We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyse data about web page traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system.

Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us. You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.

**Links to other websites**

Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.

**List of cookies we collect**

The table below lists the cookies we collect and what information they store.

**COOKIE name**

| 

**COOKIE Description**  
  
---|---  
  
**CART**

| 

The association with your shopping cart.  
  
**CATEGORY_INFO**

| 

Stores the category info on the page, that allows to display pages more quickly.  
  
**COMPARE**

| 

The items that you have in the Compare Products list.  
  
**CURRENCY**

| 

Your preferred currency  
  
**CUSTOMER**

| 

An encrypted version of your customer id with the store.  
  
**CUSTOMER_AUTH**

| 

An indicator if you are currently logged into the store.  
  
**CUSTOMER_INFO**

| 

An encrypted version of the customer group you belong to.  
  
**CUSTOMER_SEGMENT_IDS**

| 

Stores the Customer Segment ID  
  
**EXTERNAL_NO_CACHE**

| 

A flag, which indicates whether caching is disabled or not.  
  
**FRONTEND**

| 

You sesssion ID on the server.  
  
**GUEST-VIEW**

| 

Allows guests to edit their orders.  
  
**LAST_CATEGORY**

| 

The last category you visited.  
  
**LAST_PRODUCT**

| 

The most recent product you have viewed.  
  
**NEWMESSAGE**

| 

Indicates whether a new message has been received.  
  
**NO_CACHE**

| 

Indicates whether it is allowed to use cache.  
  
**PERSISTENT_SHOPPING_CART**

| 

A link to information about your cart and viewing history if you have asked the site.  
  
**POLL**

| 

The ID of any polls you have recently voted in.  
  
**POLLN**

| 

Information on what polls you have voted on.  
  
**RECENTLYCOMPARED**

| 

The items that you have recently compared.  
  
**STF**

| 

Information on products you have emailed to friends.  
  
**STORE**

| 

The store view or language you have selected.  
  
**USER_ALLOWED_SAVE_COOKIE**

| 

Indicates whether a customer allowed to use cookies.  
  
**VIEWED_PRODUCT_IDS**

| 

The products that you have recently viewed.  
  
**WISHLIST**

| 

An encrypted list of products added to your Wishlist.
